# **Andre Volpato**



andre.volpato210@gmail.com



in LinkedIn Profile

+61 416 922

© Cabarita, NSW 2137

### **EDUCATION**

## [2018 - ] **Bachelor of Enaineerina** (Mechanical),

University of New South Wales [Expected Completion - Dec 2021]

[2010 - 2017] St. Patricks College, Strathfield 92.80 ATAR Awards:

- St. Gabriel's School Award for Social Justice (2017)
- Mathematics Prize (2017)
- McGlade Scholarship (2016)

# **PROFESSIONAL MEMBERSHIPS**

Student Member of **Engineers Australia** 

#### About Me

- Sport Lover (Football [Soccer], F1, Cricket)
- Guitarist
- Runner
- Proficient in Italian Language

#### CAREER SUMMARY

A final year mechanical engineering student at UNSW who is keen to launch into an engineering internship/cadetship or graduate role for 2022 and turn study into practice, gain valuable hands-on experience and mentorship while discovering what I love to do.

For more information about myself and my academic and work involvements, please visit my **personal website** here.

#### PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

#### Administrator

De Martin & Gasparini

(DEC 2017 - PRESENT)

De Martin & Gasparini provides specialist concrete pumping and placement services for commercial and high-rise developments across the industrial, residential and utility sectors, currently including Martin Place Metro. Key Responsibilities:

- Conducted drawing change assessments for 7+ large commercial & residential projects across Sydney
- Estimate volumes of concrete from structural and architectural drawings
- Complete variation prices to provide to clients
- Created Excel spreadsheet in conjunction with project manager for cost vs. budget analysis
- Collate quality assurance documentation

#### **Support Worker**

Hireup

(MAR 2021 - PRESENT)

#### **Crew Member**

**McDonald's Westfield Burwood** 

(NOV 2014 - OCT 2016)

#### SKILLS

- Microsoft Office (Excel, Word, PowerPoint)
- Adobe Acrobat
- Solidworks
- Autodesk Fusion 360
- ANSYS Workbench (Finite Element Analysis and CFX)
- MATLAB + Simulink